http://interpret.cyracom.com/cyracom-terms-and-privacy/

1. DEFINITIONS
The “CyraCom Web site” is the interactive online service operated by CyraCom International, Inc. (CyraCom) on the World Wide Web of the Internet, consisting of information services and content provided by CyraCom, affiliates of CyraCom and other third parties. “Visitor” means each person who establishes or accesses a connection (“Account”) for access to and use of the CyraCom Web site.
2. GENERAL
(A) This Agreement, which incorporates by reference other provisions applicable to use of the CyraCom Web site, including, but not limited to, supplemental terms and conditions set forth in paragraph 14 hereof (“Supplemental Terms”) governing the use of certain specific material contained in the CyraCom Web site, sets forth the terms and conditions that apply to use of CyraCom Web site. By using the CyraCom Web site (other than to read this Agreement for the first time), Visitor agrees to comply with all of the terms and conditions hereof. The right to use the CyraCom Web site is personal to Visitor and is not transferable to any other person or entity. Visitor is responsible for all use of Visitor’s Account (under any screen name or password) and for ensuring that all use of Visitor’s Account complies fully with the provisions of this Agreement. Visitor shall be responsible for protecting the confidentiality of Visitor’s password(s), if any.
(B) CyraCom shall have the right at any time to change or discontinue any aspect or feature of the CyraCom Web site, including, but not limited to, content, hours of availability, and equipment needed for access or use.
3. CHANGED TERMS
CyraCom shall have the right at any time to change or modify the terms and conditions applicable to Visitor’s use of the CyraCom Web site, or any part thereof, or to impose new conditions, including, but not limited to, adding fees and charges for use. Such changes, modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon notice thereof, which may be given by means including, but not limited to, posting on the CyraCom Web site, or by electronic or conventional mail, or by any other means by which Visitor obtains notice thereof. Any use of the CyraCom Web site by Visitor after such notice shall be deemed to constitute acceptance by Visitor of such changes, modifications or additions.
4. EQUIPMENT
Visitor shall be responsible for obtaining and maintaining all telephone, computer hardware and other equipment needed for access to and use of the CyraCom Web site and all charges related thereto.
5. VISITOR CONDUCT
(A) Visitor shall use the CyraCom Web site for lawful purposes only. Visitor shall not post or transmit through the CyraCom Web site any material which violates or infringes in any way upon the rights of others, which is unlawful, threatening, abusive, defamatory, invasive of privacy or publicity rights, vulgar, obscene, profane or otherwise objectionable, which encourages conduct that would constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability or otherwise violate any law, or which, without CyraCom’s express prior approval, contains advertising or any solicitation with respect to products or services. Any conduct by a Visitor that in CyraCom’s discretion restricts or inhibits any other Visitor from using or enjoying the CyraCom Web site will not be permitted. Visitor shall not use the CyraCom Web site to advertise or perform any commercial solicitation, including, but not limited to, the solicitation of users to become visitors of other online information services competitive with the CyraCom Web site.
(B) CyraCom Web site contains copyrighted material, trademarks and other proprietary information, including, but not limited to, text, software, photos, video, graphics, music and sound, and the entire contents of the CyraCom Web site are copyrighted as a collective work under the United States copyright laws. CyraCom owns a copyright in the selection, coordination, arrangement and enhancement of such content, as well as in the content original to it. Visitor may not modify, publish, transmit, participate in the transfer or sale, create derivative works, or in any way exploit, any of the content, in whole or in part. Visitor may download copyrighted material for Visitor’s personal use only. Except as otherwise expressly permitted under copyright law, no copying, redistribution, retransmission, publication or commercial exploitation of downloaded material will be permitted without the express permission of CyraCom and the copyright owner. In the event of any permitted copying, redistribution or publication of copyrighted material, no changes in or deletion of author attribution, trademark legend or copyright notice shall be made. Visitor acknowledges that it does not acquire any ownership rights by downloading copyrighted material.
(C) Visitor shall not upload, post or otherwise make available on the CyraCom Web site any material protected by copyright, trademark or other proprietary right without the express permission of the owner of the copyright, trademark or other proprietary right and the burden of determining that any material is not protected by copyright rests with Visitor. Visitor shall be solely liable for any damage resulting from any infringement of copyrights, proprietary rights, or any other harm resulting from such a submission. By submitting material to any public area of the CyraCom Web site, Visitor automatically grants, or warrants that the owner of such material has expressly granted CyraCom the royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive right and license to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate and distribute such material (in whole or in part) worldwide and/or to incorporate it in other works in any form, media or technology now known or hereafter developed for the full term of any copyright that may exist in such material. Visitor also permits any other Visitor to access, view, store or reproduce the material for that Visitor’s personal use. Visitor hereby grants CyraCom the right to edit, copy, publish and distribute any material made available on the CyraCom Web site by Visitor.
(D) The foregoing provisions of Section 5 are for the benefit of CyraCom, its subsidiaries, affiliates and its third party content providers and licensors and each shall have the right to assert and enforce such provisions directly or on its own behalf.
6. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY; LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
(A) SUBSCRIBER EXPRESSLY AGREES THAT USE OF CyraCom Web site IS AT SUBSCRIBER’S SOLE RISK. NEITHER CyraCom, ITS AFFILIATES NOR ANY OF THEIR RESPECTIVE EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, THIRD PARTY CONTENT PROVIDERS OR LICENSORS WARRANT THAT CyraCom Web site WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE; NOR DO THEY MAKE ANY WARRANTY AS TO THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM USE OF CyraCom Web site, OR AS TO THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY OR CONTENT OF ANY INFORMATION, SERVICE, OR MERCHANDISE PROVIDED THROUGH CyraCom Web site.
(B) CyraCom Web site IS PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” BASIS WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF TITLE OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OTHER THAN THOSE WARRANTIES WHICH ARE IMPLIED BY AND INCAPABLE OF EXCLUSION, RESTRICTION OR MODIFICATION UNDER THE LAWS APPLICABLE TO THIS AGREEMENT.
(C) THIS DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY APPLIES TO ANY DAMAGES OR INJURY CAUSED BY ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DELETION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS, COMMUNICATION LINE FAILURE, THEFT OR DESTRUCTION OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO, ALTERATION OF, OR USE OF RECORD, WHETHER FOR BREACH OF CONTRACT, TORTIOUS BEHAVIOR, NEGLIGENCE, OR UNDER ANY OTHER CAUSE OF ACTION. SUBSCRIBER SPECIFICALLY ACKNOWLEDGES THAT CyraCom IS NOT LIABLE FOR THE DEFAMATORY, OFFENSIVE OR ILLEGAL CONDUCT OF OTHER SUBSCRIBERS OR THIRD-PARTIES AND THAT THE RISK OF INJURY FROM THE FOREGOING RESTS ENTIRELY WITH SUBSCRIBER.
(D) IN NO EVENT WILL CyraCom, OR ANY PERSON OR ENTITY INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING OR DISTRIBUTING CyraCom Web site OR THE CyraCom Web site SOFTWARE, BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE CyraCom Web site. SUBSCRIBER HEREBY ACKNOWLEDGES THAT THE PROVISIONS OF THIS SECTION SHALL APPLY TO ALL CONTENT ON CyraCom Web site.
(E) IN ADDITION TO THE TERMS SET FORTH ABOVE NEITHER, CyraCom, NOR ITS AFFILIATES, INFORMATION PROVIDERS OR CONTENT PARTNERS SHALL BE LIABLE REGARDLESS OF THE CAUSE OR DURATION, FOR ANY ERRORS, INACCURACIES, OMISSIONS, OR OTHER DEFECTS IN, OR UNTIMELINESS OR UNAUTHENTICITY OF, THE INFORMATION CONTAINED WITHIN CyraCom Web site, OR FOR ANY DELAY OR INTERRUPTION IN THE TRANSMISSION THEREOF TO THE USER, OR FOR ANY CLAIMS OR LOSSES ARISING THEREFROM OR OCCASIONED THEREBY. NONE OF THE FOREGOING PARTIES SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY THIRD-PARTY CLAIMS OR LOSSES OF ANY NATURE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, LOST PROFITS, PUNITIVE OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. PRIOR TO THE EXECUTION OF A STOCK TRADE, SUBSCRIBERS ARE ADVISED TO CONSULT WITH YOUR BROKER OR OTHER FINANCIAL REPRESENTATIVE TO VERIFY PRICING OR OTHER INFORMATION. CyraCom, ITS AFFILIATES, INFORMATION PROVIDERS OR CONTENT PARTNERS SHALL HAVE NO LIABILITY FOR INVESTMENT DECISIONS BASED ON THE INFORMATION PROVIDED. NEITHER, CyraCom, NOR ITS AFFILIATES, INFORMATION PROVIDERS OR CONTENT PARTNERS WARRANT OR GUARANTEE THE TIMELINESS, SEQUENCE, ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF THIS INFORMATION. ADDITIONALLY, THERE ARE NO WARRANTIES AS TO THE RESULTS OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE INFORMATION.
7. MONITORING
CyraCom shall have the right, but not the obligation, to monitor the content of CyraCom Web site, including chat rooms and forums, to determine compliance with this Agreement and any operating rules established by CyraCom and to satisfy any law, regulation or authorized government request. CyraCom shall have the right in its sole discretion to edit, refuse to post or remove any material submitted to or posted on CyraCom Web site. Without limiting the foregoing, CyraCom shall have the right to remove any material that CyraCom, in its sole discretion, finds to be in violation of the provisions hereof or otherwise objectionable.
8. INDEMNIFICATION
Visitor agrees to defend, indemnify and hold harmless CyraCom, its affiliates and their respective directors, officers, employees and agents from and against all claims and expenses, including attorneys’ fees, arising out of the use of CyraCom Web site by Visitor or Visitor’s Account.
9. TERMINATION
Either CyraCom or Visitor may terminate this Agreement at any time. Without limiting the foregoing, CyraCom shall have the right to immediately terminate Visitor’s Account in the event of any conduct by Visitor which CyraCom, in its sole discretion, considers to be unacceptable, or in the event of any breach by Subscriber of this Agreement. The provisions of Sections 5(B), 5(C), 5(D), 6, 8, 10 and this Section 9 shall survive termination of this Agreement.
10. TRADEMARKS
CyraCom, CyraCom Web site and each of their logos are trademarks of CyraCom International, Inc. All rights reserved. All other trademarks appearing on CyraCom Web site are the property of their respective owners.
11. THIRD PARTY CONTENT
CyraCom is a distributor (and not a publisher) of content supplied by third parties and Visitors. Accordingly, CyraCom has no more editorial control over such content than does a public library, bookstore, or newsstand. Any opinions, advice, statements, services, offers, or other information or content expressed or made available by third parties, including information providers, Visitors or any other user of CyraCom Web site, are those of the respective author(s) or distributor(s) and not of CyraCom. Neither CyraCom nor any third-party provider of information guarantees the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any content, nor its merchantability or fitness for any particular purpose. (Refer to Section 6 above for the complete provisions governing limitation of liabilities and disclaimers of warranty.)
In many instances, the content available through the CyraCom Web site represents the opinions and judgments of the respective information provider, Visitor, or other user not under contract with CyraCom. CyraCom neither endorses nor is responsible for the accuracy or reliability of any opinion, advice or statement made on the CyraCom Web site by anyone other than authorized CyraCom employee spokespersons while acting in their official capacities. Under no circumstances will CyraCom be liable for any loss or damage caused by a Visitor’s reliance on information obtained through the CyraCom Web site. It is the responsibility of Visitor to evaluate the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any information, opinion, advice or other content available through CyraCom Web site. Please seek the advice of professionals, as appropriate, regarding the evaluation of any specific information, opinion, advice or other content.
12. MISCELLANEOUS
This Agreement and any operating rules for the CyraCom Web site established by CyraCom constitute the entire agreement of the parties with respect to the subject matter hereof, and supersede all previous written or oral agreements between the parties with respect to such subject matter. This Agreement shall be construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Arizona, without regard to its conflict of laws rules. No waiver by either party of any breach or default hereunder shall be deemed to be a waiver of any preceding or subsequent breach or default. The section headings used herein are for convenience only and shall not be given any legal import.
13. COPYRIGHTS AND COPYRIGHT AGENT
CyraCom respects the rights of all copyright holders and in this regard, CyraCom has adopted and implemented a policy that provides for the termination in appropriate circumstances of subscribers and account holders who infringe the rights of copyright holders. If you believe that your work has been copied in a way that constitutes copyright infringement, please provide CyraCom’s Copyright Agent the following information required by the Online Copyright Infringement Liability Limitation Act of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, 17 U.S.C. 512:
A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;
Identification of the copyright work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works at a single online site are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works at that site;
Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material;
Information reasonably sufficient to permit us to contact the complaining party;
A statement that the complaining party has a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and
A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
CyraCom’s Copyright Agent for notice of claims of copyright infringement on or regarding this site can be reached as follows:
Copyright Agent
VP of Marketing
CyraCom International, Inc.
5780 N. Swan Rd.
Tucson, AZ 85718
14. SUPPLEMENTAL TERMS
None.
PRIVACY POLICY
Effective Date: February 20, 2019
Thank you for visiting the CyraCom Website. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we have provided this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
1. INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT
On this site, you can request information, subscribe to our services, register for events, and sign up for our newsletter. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.
We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows 7, Mac OS), and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Comcast, AT&T).
2. HOW WE MAY USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, events, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs, events, or services that we believe may be of interest to you.
We may use this information to communicate with you when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.
We may use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, events, or services.
We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by valid legal authority, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. Additionally, we may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request.
Agents and contractors of CyraCom who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by refraining from using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for CyraCom.
Although CyraCom takes measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we do not guarantee that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.
CyraCom may, on occasion, combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, please email marketing@cyracom.com for instructions on how to make your request.
This site respects the do-not-track settings on browsers and will not track your activity if such feature is engaged on your browser.
Finally, CyraCom sites will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.
3. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD-PARTY SITES AND SPONSORS
CyraCom may offer promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the promotion. CyraCom has no control over the third-party sponsors’ use of this information. CyraCom will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if third-party sponsors will obtain such information.
CyraCom does not allow third-party tracking on its Website(s).
4. COOKIES
To enhance your experience at CyraCom, many of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering on one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.
We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience on our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site) or save your password in password-protected areas. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.
5. THE CYRACOM MOBILE APPLICATION
In addition to the entirety of this privacy policy, the following terms also apply to the CyraCom Mobile Application and Web Video Interpretation:
The Information We Collect
By using the application, CyraCom may collect information including user e-mail address, password, account and pin information, optional call information fields that pass through the app to CyraCom servers but are not stored on the mobile device, and a history log of calls.
How We Use the Information
We may use the information to track service utilization, to conduct billing, for authentication purposes, and/or to improve usability. This data will not be disclosed to third parties except as required by valid legal authority.
Our Commitment to Security on the CyraCom Mobile Application
Our mobile application and web interpretation services will not transmit any data about a user without first obtaining the user’s permission. If you have any further questions, please contact us at privacy@cyracom.com..
6.	TRANSLATION SERVICES
In addition to the entirety of this privacy policy, the following terms also apply to the CyraCom Customer Portal used for Translation and Localization services.
The Information We Collect
By using the portal, CyraCom may collect information including user e-mail address, password, and the content of the document(s) being translated.
How We Use the Information
We may use the information to track service utilization, to conduct billing, for authentication purposes, and/or to improve usability. By uploading documents, you grant CyraCom consent to access, store, and transmit the contents of the document for the provision of translation services. You also consent to the storage of the document to aid in future translation projects.
Our Commitment to Security on the CyraCom Customer Portal
CyraCom will not transmit any data about a user without first obtaining the user’s permission. If you have any further questions, please contact us at
privacy@cyracom.com..
7.	OUR COMMITMENT TO SECURITY
CyraCom has put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard personally identifiable information and prevent unauthorized access thereto, maintain data security, and prevent improper use of the information we collect online.
Additionally, CyraCom complies with COPPA and children’s issues as this Website and the CyraCom mobile application are not directed to children under the age of thirteen (13), and children may not use our services.
8.	HOW YOU CAN ACCESS OR CORRECT INFORMATION
For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that CyraCom has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please contact us at privacy@cyracom.com..
Users may also contact CyraCom if services ordered are terminated and/or you want to delete or withdraw consent.
To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
9.	CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT
If we implement or make changes to our privacy policy, the changes will be posted on our website and will be distributed to any organizations that maintain this information (e.g. the US Department of Commerce).
10.	HOW TO CONTACT CYRACOM
If you have any questions or concerns about the CyraCom privacy policy for this site or its implementation, please contact us at privacy@cyracom.com. or at the following phone number or mailing address:
Privacy Officer
5780 N. Swan Rd.
Tucson, AZ 85718
(520) 745-9447
CyraCom has published COVID-19 Language Access Resources and additional information about our business continuity plan.  Learn More
